

Jayath Malaka Jayasekara

Undergraduate Student

- ☑ ginkahagame@gmail.com 🤳 +94715856749
- 15/32, 3rd lane, koswatta road, nawala, 10100 Colombo

Profile

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for Marketing. I am currently in my final year of studying BSc Business Management in Marketing at ICBT Campus. I am seeing a full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for in order to gain work experience and training. I lived and stayed in India for about 8 years from Grade I to 8 (year 2005 to 2012).

Education

Edexcel O/Levels Sep 2013 - Sep 2015

Colombo South International College, Kalubowila

London Commerce Stream

International Foundation Diploma Jan 2016 - Aug 2017

Gateway College, Rajagiriya Information Technology

Higher National Diploma in Business Mar 2018 - Jul 2020

Management

ICBT Campus, Bambalapitiya

Marketing

Higher National Diploma in Information Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Technology

ICBT Campus, Bambalapitiya

Software Engineering

BSc. Business Management in Marketing Nov 2021 - Nov 2022

ICBT Campus, Bambalapitiya

Cardiff Metropolitan University

Employment

Computer Operator - Internship Aug 2020 - Jul 2021

Installation Team, Nawala

Photonics Lighting Pvt Ltd

Data Entry Clerk - Internship Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

Data Entry Operations Team, Kollupitiya

Trickle Amistad Pvt Ltd

Personal details

Date of birth December 25, 1998

Place of birth Mirigama

Gender

Male

Nationality

Sri Lankan

Civil status

Unmarried

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jayathmalak ajayasekara-117387135

NIC Number 199836010908

Languages

English

Hindi

Kannada

Sinhala

Skills

Strong verbal and written communication skills

Ability to translate complex research into common language

Junior Marketing Executive

Management Trainee, Kollupitiya

Manpower Sri Lanka Recruitment Consultant

Proficiency with word processing, spreadsheet and presentation software

Aptitude with various social media platforms as well as the data tracking tools associated with them

Ability to quickly learn and process information

Organization and time management skills

Hobbies

- Meditation
- Learning Musical Instruments
- Cooking
- Reading
- Puzzle Solving
- Writing
- Gardening
- Cycling
- Gym

Qualities

- Creative & Passionate
- Good Listener & Reader
- Responsible and Kind
- Honest and Integrity
- Ethical and Loyal
- Punctual & Flexible
- Team player & Strategic thinking

Extracurricular activities

Leo Club of Nawala Metro

Volunteer, Colombo

Social Service

Badminton

Aug 2016 - Jul 2017

Apr 2018 - Dec 2018

Dec 2021 - Jul 2022

Nawala

Cricket Jan 2014 - Mar 2015

Colombo

Taekwondo Sep 2010 - Sep 2011

Bangalore Karate

Art and Craft Mar 2006 - Jul 2009

Bangalore

Team Member Mar 2019 - May 2019

Volunteer, Bambalapitiya

Leadership Workshop at ICBT Campus

Achievements

English Literature Essay Writing Competition second place

School Arts and Crafts Competition 2nd place

References

J.K.S Jayanetti

Lecturer at Open University, Nawala 0776874400

N.D.A Harshana Gunasekara

Lecturer at Moratuwa University, Colombo 0716130233